http://www.smittenpets.com.au/pages/privacy

Newsletter
Be the first to see new products and discounts.
Dogs
ToysLeadsCollarsClothingBowlsBeds & BlanketsGroomingAccessoriesDry FoodTreatsHealth CareCats
ToysCollars & AccessoriesBeds & GroomingBowlsDry FoodTreatsHealth CareFood
Cat'sDog'sDry Food - complete feed
CatDogTreat'sGluten FreeGrain FreeBeefChickenDuckKangarooLambSeafoodPet Care
Cat'sDog'sWormer'sFlea TreatmentTick TreatmentHeartwormMonthly treatment3 Monthly TreatmentSupplements Owners
Gifts & BooksJewellery & CufflinksSearch by Size of your Dog
X Small DogSmall DogsMedium DogLarge DogX Large DogXX Large DogXXX Large DogPet Taxi
Book Pet TaxiAbout usCheckout
Smitten Pets respects your privacy and information. When you purchase from our store, as part of the buying and selling process you give information like name, address and email. The information we gather will be used by Smitten Pets, or if third parties are present, only for the purpose of ensuring the best levels of customer service. When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address to helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
We will only make contact with you for customer service purposes, and when you have opted in to special offers and promotions. You may choose not to receive these types of notifications. If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at info@smittenpets.com.au
Links and Third Parties: Please be aware that Smitten Pets is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites that may be linked on Smitten Pets. This includes third parties like a third party gateway that you might use. We recommend you understand their privacy policies.  Remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us and your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located. As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act. Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
DISCLOSURE
We may disclose your personal information to courier companies to fulfil your order, suppliers if they deliver direct to your door and if we are required by law to do so.
Payment: If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, your credit card data is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.
Google analytics: Our store may use Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being looked at.
SECURITY
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.
Cookies: A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use cookies to record the details of your order, time on page and if you have been referred to us. These cookies are not shared with any other sites.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it. If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us at info@smittenpets.com.au.
Subscribe to our newsletter
Be the first to see new products and discounts.
100% free, Unsubscribe any time!
Free delivery
For purchases over $100.
Satisfied or refunded
Should you not be satisfied with the quality on receipt of your purchase, we will provide you with a refund.
Top-notch support
If you are sure what you need, or looking for something not shown we are always happy to assist.
Secure payments
Various payment  options are available, such as; Paypal, Layby and Afterpay.
